## Kristopher Sinclair

2401 Windy Hill Road Se Marietta, Ga 30067 404-396-9939 anthonybusinessall@icloud.com

#### **Profile:**

Product line specialist and supervisor with over 11 years experience across multiple departments. Balanced multiple project deadlines while able to maintain a sense of humor and poise under pressure. Talent for mentoring and training new teammates. Record for launching ideas into tangible support support projects to drive efficiency. Unparalleled motivation has led to various positions of leadership, lateral initiatives, and responsibilities requiring elevated emotional and social intelligence.

#### **Experience:**

### <u>Apilson (Front Desk)</u> 2021 - Present

- Excel spreadsheets updated, M.O.D. reports created, both emailed to management daily
- Invoice and bill guest for stay and services used, accommodate guest requests
- Handle and resolve guest complaints, check in/ check out, wake up calls
- Confirm bookings via 3rd party websites, pass on relevant info at shift change

#### <u> Apple Inc. 2012 - Present</u>

- Promoted to Health Support. A new initiative launched summer 2020
- Selected for Agreement Admin +. Escalation point for all coverages sold
- Promoted to Mac Plus Tier 2. Manage final point of contact responsibilities

- Selected for Apple Solutions Consultant. Marketed Apple Watch in Best Buy
- Selected and certified as an FRS Specialist. Inspected iPhones and all Macs
- Trained and provisioned for Apple's Safety queue; Account Security; Apple Watch
- Promoted as an Accessibility advisor. Managed technical escalations via RTA's with SSE
- Presented/scribed at Team meetings; Created Keynotes/organized training materials
- Recognized by Apple as a top performer with customer satisfaction 2 quarters in a row
- Recognized and Awarded for top sales in division for AC+
- Project Manager for Team Newsletter for 3 years. Promoted to the Senior Area Newsletter

#### Sitel for Apple Inc. 2010-2011

- Provided first point of contact technical support to Apple customers
- Recognized for perfect attendance, selling most APP's, contributing most overtime.
- Trained new associates. Prepared content for meetings. Shared best practices
- Leveraged workforce mobility to promote awareness, assist in troubleshooting, conduct pilots/testing, and improve communication/sales strategies

#### <u>Direct Buy Call Center.</u> 2009

- Promoted to assistant warehouse manager. Inventory inspection, update Sku
- Created and implemented scenario-based training for new hires across multiple platforms
- Inspect all merchandise coming in and out of warehouse
- Following up with customers, pre-sales and post-sales, via email and phone
- Assist in training new employees in proper phone etiquette, how to use phone systems

 Achieved and exceeded call center metrics. Regularly a top performer and awarded often

# **Education**

Columbia Southern University Bachelors 2021

College of Southern Nevada Associates 2016